<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Robin Candau</title>
    <link>https://antiz.fr/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Robin Candau</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 18:35:13 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://antiz.fr/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Automatically power back on servers after a power outage with a Raspberry Pi and Wake On Lan</title>
      <link>https://antiz.fr/blog/raspberry-pi-wake-on-lan-server/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 18:35:13 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antiz.fr/blog/raspberry-pi-wake-on-lan-server/</guid>
      
        <description>Context I recently woke up with a non working network connection in my house, both internet and LAN accesses were down.
I immediately checked on my internet provider but my router seemed running just fine and no breakages were reported on their side in my region.
I then decided to check on my own infrastructure and realised that both of my physical servers were down.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The automated workflow I use to manage this website</title>
      <link>https://antiz.fr/blog/website_workflow/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 13:20:26 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antiz.fr/blog/website_workflow/</guid>
      
        <description>The website This website is built with the HUGO static website generator using the anatole theme.
The website&amp;rsquo;s source code is hosted in this GitHub repository.
Automated workflow To manage this website, I use an automated workflow based upon CI/CD (Continuous Integration/Continuous Delivery).
CI I make my changes (creating an article, update the theme, add new parameters to the website, etc&amp;hellip;) locally on my computer inside the git repository in the dev branch.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to antiz.fr!</title>
      <link>https://antiz.fr/blog/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 15:55:47 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://antiz.fr/blog/welcome/</guid>
      
        <description>As stated in the home page, this website serves as a central place to get general/contact info about me. It also contains a list to all my social media.
If you want to contact me, reach me at robincandau@protonmail.com, @Antiz96 on Twitter or Antiz#4953 on Discord.
I&amp;rsquo;ll use this blog section to publish some blog posts when I feel like it.</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>